<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Space Explorer</string>
    <string name="button_text">Show Details</string>
    <string name="mercury_details">Mercury is the closest planet to the Sun and the smallest planet in our solar system. It has a very thin atmosphere and extreme temperature variations. Mercury has a heavily cratered surface, similar to Earth\'s moon, and experiences wild temperature fluctuations, ranging from extremely hot during the day to freezing cold at night.</string>
    <string name="venus_details">Venus is the second planet from the Sun and has a thick, toxic atmosphere. It is known for its extreme surface temperatures and volcanic activity. Venus\'s atmosphere is primarily composed of carbon dioxide, with clouds of sulfuric acid, making it the hottest planet in our solar system with surface temperatures high enough to melt lead.</string>
    <string name="earth_details">Earth is the third planet from the Sun and the only planet known to support life. It has a diverse climate and ecosystems. Earth has a vast array of life forms and a dynamic surface with continents that move and change shape over geological time scales, a stable climate, and a protective atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="mars_details">Mars is the fourth planet from the Sun and is often called the Red Planet due to its reddish appearance. It has the largest volcano and canyon in the solar system. Mars has a thin atmosphere, composed mostly of carbon dioxide, and its surface is covered with iron oxide dust and rocks. Mars has seasons, polar ice caps, and evidence of ancient river valleys and lake beds.</string>
    <string name="jupiter_details">Jupiter is the fifth planet from the Sun and the largest planet in our solar system. It is known for its Great Red Spot, a giant storm, and its many moons. Jupiter is a gas giant composed primarily of hydrogen and helium, with a massive magnetic field and at least 79 moons, including the four large Galilean moons: Io, Europa, Ganymede, and Callisto.</string>
    <string name="saturn_details">Saturn is the sixth planet from the Sun and is famous for its prominent ring system. It has numerous moons, including Titan, which has a thick atmosphere. Saturn is a gas giant composed mainly of hydrogen and helium, with an extensive and complex ring system made of ice particles, rocky debris, and dust. Titan, its largest moon, is larger than Mercury and has a dense atmosphere rich in nitrogen.</string>
    <string name="uranus_details">Uranus is the seventh planet from the Sun and has a unique blue-green color due to methane in its atmosphere. It rotates on its side, making its seasons extreme. Uranus is an ice giant with an atmosphere composed of hydrogen, helium, and methane. It has faint rings, a rocky core, and 27 known moons. Its axial tilt of 98 degrees results in extreme seasonal changes.</string>
    <string name="neptune_details">Neptune is the eighth and farthest planet from the Sun, known for its deep blue color. It has strong winds and storms, and its moon Triton has geysers. Neptune is an ice giant with a dynamic atmosphere featuring the fastest winds in the solar system, reaching speeds of up to 1,200 miles per hour. Triton, its largest moon, is geologically active with geysers that erupt nitrogen gas.</string>
</resources>
